

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To learn and gain the required experience in related areas with a long-term goal of being in any related field. Utilize my education background and skills in my job and responsibilities in order to ensure the company grow and achieve success continuously.

PERSONAL PARTICULARS

Name : Lance Laing Jau Ic Number : 890122-13-5825 Age : 25 years old

Date of Birth : 22nd JANUARY 1989

Place of Birth : SARAWAK
Gender : Male
Marital Status : Single
Nationality : Malaysian
Religion : Christian
Health : Excellent

Language Proficiency : Malay / English / Mandarin E-Mail : lancelaingjau89@gmail.com

Address : No 0207, Block 11 Bandar Selesa Jaya, Johor Bahru,

81110 , Johor

Expected Salary : RM 2200.00

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

YEAR	QUALIFICATION	INSTITUTION
2012	Oracle Certificate, JAVA SCJP , SCWCD	Pusat Latihan Industri Johor PUSPATRI.
2007 - 2010	Diploma in Information of Technology CGPA: 3.43	Institut Sains dan Teknologi Darul Takzim,Kota Tinggi
2006	Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM) (7 Credits)	Sek. Men Keb. Riam Miri Taman Tunku,Miri,Sarawak.
2004	Penilaian Menengah Rendah (PMR)	Sek. Men. Keb. Riam Miri.

WORKING EXPERIENCES

1)

Company : Tekvent Sdn Bhd

(Oct 2012 - Feb 2014)

Department : Programming
Position : Sql Programmer

Working Scope : Sql Salary : RM1800

2)

Company : Telekom Malaysia.

(Aug 2010 – Aug 2011)-Leasing Worker

Department : Customer Service Management JB(CSM)
Position : Technical Assistant (Flying Squad)

Scope : Technical, Networking.

Salary : RM1200/Month

3)

Company : Perbadanan Perpustakaan Awam Johor(PPAJ)

(Dec 2009 - May 2010)-Practical student

Department : Information Technology

Position : IT Technician

Working Scope : Control all electronic item

Salary : No salary.

INTEREST

- -Computer
- -Sports
- -Travelling

COMPUTER SKILLS

Operating System : Windows

Software : Eclipse, SqlYog, Microsoft Office,etc.

Computer Maintanance : Computer Hardware Installation, Format Hard Drive,

Operating System Installation, Software Installation, Network

Installation, etc.

REFEREES

NAME : Mr. Aminnudin Ami

TELEPHONE NO. : 013-7594070

EMAIL : aminuddin.ami89@gmail.com

POSITION : Senior IT Executive (Tekvent Sdn Bhd)